<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Warsaw Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="malls">Malls</string>
    <string name="galleries">Galleries</string>
    <string name="cinemas">Cinemas</string>
    <string name="shops">Shops</string>

    <string name="star_vines">Star Wines Poland</string>
    <string name="star_vines_description">There are more than 400 wines from the
                whole world available for retail purchase at Star Wines Poland  manufactured both by the most highly acknowledged
                producers and niche vineyards; the award-winning wine selection
                recognized by the prestigious Wine Spectator will make for a good purchase</string>
    <string name="olimpia_bazaar">Olimpia Bazaar</string>
    <string name="olimpia_bazaar_description">Within a week, there is a sports club in here
                On Sunday, the stadium turns into a big market. On Olympia, the bazaar at Górczewska street you can buy antiquities, clothing and tools.
                Old newspapers, books, that you can not get up even in antique shops, used shoes - it all adds up to a peculiar charm of this place</string>
    <string name="kino_muranow">Kino Muranow</string>
    <string name="kino_muranow_description">In 2004, Kino Muranow won the “Europa Cinemas Award” for Best
                Cinema in Europe in terms of repertoire. Among this repertoire, you can find an English
                Friendly Movie Cycle of non-English movies (including Polish movies) with English subtitles.</string>
    <string name="kino_wisla">Kino Wisla</string>
    <string name="kino_wisla_description">Kino Wisła also organizes Polish Film For Foreigners, a super
                cool series of screening about (you guessed it) Polish Movies with English subtitles.
                After the screenings, there are usually meetings with the actors or with the director of the movie.</string>

    <string name="national_muzeum">National Museum in Warsaw</string>
    <string name="national_muzeum_des">The National Museum in
                Warsaw was founded in 1862 as the Museum of Fine Arts and is one of the oldest museums in Poland.
                The modernist building where it`s located currently was built between 1927-1938 and it`s
                one of the most important buildings of that time in Warsaw (Tadeusz Tołwiński`s project).</string>
    <string name="zacheta">Zachęta – National Gallery of Art</string>
    <string name="zacheta_des">Zachęta is one of the oldest galleries in Poland.
                The beautiful building was constructed between 1898-1900 according to project of Stefan Szyller.
                Gallery presented all the most important Polish artists’ including Wojciech Gerson, Jan Matejko, Józef Chełmoński,
                or Stanisław Wyspiański.</string>
    <string name="muz_on_the_wis">Museum on the Vistula – Museum of Modern Art</string>
    <string name="muz_on_the_wis_des">The Museum on the Vistula is a new exhibition
                pavilion of the Museum of Modern Art in Warsaw. It`s located at Wybrzeże
                Kościuszkowskie 22, next to the Copernicus Science Center and Vistula river</string>
    <string name="fokzal">Foksal Gallery</string>
    <string name="fokzal_des">Foksal Gallery was founded in 1966 so it`s the oldest and one of the most
                prominent galleries of modern art in Poland. The gallery is focused on searching out and
                highlighting radical approaches to contemporary art.</string>

    <string name="halakosz">Hala Koszyki</string>
    <string name="halakosz_des">Eighteen fabulous restaurant concepts,
                eleven fantastic groceries and service premises - Warsaws Śródmieście
                regained its lost pearl. Hala Koszyki is the first and the only place of its kind in whole Poland.</string>

    <string name="arkadia">Westfield Arkadia Shopping Mall</string>
    <string name="arkadia_des">There is a nice food court and
                lots of shops including Polish clothing stores. All in all a great selection of stores.
                Outside there is a beautiful playground for kids. This is a great place to shop for clothes,
                luggage, food, etc. There is a taxi stand nearby but taxis seldom come by.</string>

    <string name="zlote_tar">Zlote Tarasy</string>
    <string name="zlote_tar_des">Huge shopping complex. Designer brands,
                prices slightly higher than other European destinations. Large variety of food outlets on top floors.
                Had some wonderful Turkish food there. Easy access from central station.</string>

    <string name="galeria_mok">Galeria Mokotow</string>
    <string name="galeria_mok_des">Almost 250 shops on several floors make Galeria Mokotow one
                of the largest shopping centers in Warsaw. Visitors may have to take a tram or bus to reach it.</string>

</resources>
